Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive 1989-2004 MSS 191
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series III: No Alternative
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1993 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series V: Red Hot + Country
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Helene Silverman (Restricted), 1993 - 1994 (Box [46])
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.] (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1994 - 1995 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.] (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0005)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, 1994 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0006)
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Country, 1994 (Box 32, Object ID: 191.2.0007)
- Oversize Series VI: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters - Red Hot + Cool & Red Hot On Impulse, [n.d.] (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1994 (Box [46])
    - Promotional sampler featuring "The Rubbers Song" by The Pharcyde and "Proceed II" by The Roots with Roy Ayers; Red Hot Organization, 1994 (Box 42)
    - Promotional sampler featuring special new mixes by The Roots and Da Beatminerz; Red Hot Organization, 1995 (Box 43)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photographs: GRP publicity shots / Craftsmen photo, [n.d.] (Box [46])
    - Photographs: Color + B&W, [n.d.] (Box [46])
    - Photographs: Stolen Moments Color + B&W, [n.d.] (Box [46])
    - Oversize Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered
      - Subseries B: Promotional Material
        - Posters - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Subseries D: Merchandise
        - Red Hot + Bothered EP's with limited edition fanzines, Volume I Number 1; Red Hot Organization, 1995 (Box 44)
          Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 10 in.
        - Red Hot + Bothered EP's with limited edition fanzines, Volume I Number 2; Red Hot Organization, 1995 (Box 44)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot on Impulse double vinyl; GRP Records, 1994 (Box 43)
    - Single: "Proceed II," The Roots with Roy Ayers; Red Hot Organization, 1995 (Box 43)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool double vinyl; GRP Records, 1994 (Box 43)
      Sound Disc, Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
- Oversize Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, [n.d.]
  - Subseries B: Promotional Materials
    - Posters- Red Hot + Bothered, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Oversize Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
  - Subseries B: Promotional Materials
    - Poster - Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip (Box [45], Folder [14])
    - Poster- The Beat Experience, [n.d] (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Offbeat: The Red Hot Remixes; Red Hot Organization, 1996 (Box 42)
    - T-Shirt: Offbeat, [n.d.] (Box 33, Object ID: 191.2.0008)
- Oversize Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - In-store play sampler; EastWest Records America, 1996 (Box 43)
    - Posters - America Is Dying Slowly, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 1996
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - America Is Dying Slowly vinyl sleeve, 1996 (Box 43)
    - T-shirts - America Is Dying Slowly, [n.d.] (Box 33, Object ID: 191.2.0009)
- Oversize Series X: Red Hot + Rio
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1996 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirt - Red Hot + Rio, [n.d.] (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0010)
- Oversize Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Invoice: Scarlett Letters, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1997 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirt - Silencio=Muerte, [n.d.] (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0011)
- Oversize Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute")
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1997 - 1998 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series XIII: Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon, 1998 - 1999
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 1998 - 1999
    - Posters - Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Press reviews, 1998 - 1999 (Box [46])
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - T-shirts - Red Hot + Lisbon, [n.d.] (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0012)
- Oversize Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Poster sign - Red Hot + Rhapsody, [n.d.] (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 1998 (Box [46])
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, in collaboration with Levi's; Antilles Records, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody double vinyl; Verve Records, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Oversize Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
    - Subseries A: Production Files
      - Invoices: CD&L, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Subseries B: Promotional Material
      - Posters, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Press clippings: General, 1993-1998 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Press clippings: 10th anniversary - ArtForum, November 2000 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Subseries D: Merchandise
      - "One," U2: AIDS research benefit album featuring photograph by David Wojnarowicz on cover; Island Records, 1992 (Box 42)
      - T-shirt - "everybody", [n.d.] (Box 34, Object ID: 191.2.0013)
      - T-shirts - Red Hot Organization contributers, c.a. 1994 (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0014)
      - T-shirt - safer sex is hot sex, female couple, [n.d.] (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0015)
      - T-shirt - safer sex is hot sex, male couple, [n.d.] (Box 35, Object ID: 191.2.0016)
- Oversize Series XVI: Red Hot + Indigo
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 2001 (Box [46])
- Oversize Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Posters - Red Hot + Riot, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Sampler featuring "Gentlemen," "Shakara/Lady" and "Zombie [Part One];" MCA Records, 2002 (Box 43)
    - Sampler featuring "Water No Get Enemy," "Fela Mentality" and "Shuffering + Shmiling;" MCA Records, 2002 (Box 43)
- Oversize Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
  - Subseries A: Administration Files
    - Invoice: CD&L, 2000-01 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Subseries B: Promotional Materials
      - Posters - General, 1997-98 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Press Clippings - General, 1993-98 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Press Clippings - 10th Anniversary - Art Forum, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 13)